What's best: a brand new phone or a day out with your friends?
什么更好：一部全新的手机，还是和朋友出去玩一天？
Is it better to spend money to buy things or to do things?
把钱花在买东西上更好，还是花在体验事情上更好？
A study of UK consumers showed that six in ten people would rather spend their money on experiences than material possessions.
一项针对英国消费者的研究表明，十分之六的人更愿意把钱花在体验上，而不是物质财产上。
Those aged 18-34 reported spending the highest amount on fun activities.
18至34岁的人群报告称，他们在有趣的活动上花费最多。
Possessions can last for many years, while experiences are fleeting.
物质财产可以持续很多年，而体验却是短暂的。
This, however, might be the wrong way to look at things.
然而，这可能是看待事物的错误方式。
Psychology professor Thomas Gilovich discovered that the happiness that objects provide can fade quickly.
心理学教授托马斯·吉洛维奇发现，物品带来的幸福感会迅速消退。
We adapt to having new possessions, so that rather than being something we are excited by, they just become our new normal.
我们会适应拥有新物品，因此它们不再是我们为之兴奋的东西，而只是成为我们的新常态。
Soon we may even want to buy a better version of the things we own.
很快，我们甚至可能想买自己拥有的东西的更好版本。
Our feelings around possessions can also be affected by others.
我们对物质财产的感受也会受到他人的影响。
We tend to compare what we have with other people.
我们倾向于将自己的东西与他人进行比较。
If someone else has something better, we can start to feel envious.
如果别人有更好的东西，我们就会开始感到嫉妒。
A holiday or a day out may have a short duration, but the happiness it provides can last much longer.
一个假期或一天的短途旅行可能持续时间很短，但它带来的快乐却能持续更久。
Waiting for our latest purchases to be delivered is frustrating, but waiting for an exciting event gives us a feeling of anticipation.
等待我们最新购买的物品送达会令人沮丧，但等待一个激动人心的活动会给我们一种期待感。
Experiences are often shared, so we gain pleasure from social connection and time spent with other people.
体验往往是共享的，所以我们从社交联系和与他人共度的时光中获得快乐。
Memories of our experiences become part of our identity.
我们对经历的回忆成为我们身份的一部分。
As Gilovich points out, we are the sum of our experiences.
正如吉洛维奇指出的那样，我们是所有经历的总和。
Indeed, the very fact that experiences last for a limited time can give them value.
事实上，体验的持续时间有限这一事实本身就能赋予它们价值。
A physical good deteriorates over time, while our memories of an experience can give us pleasure year after year.
有形商品会随着时间的推移而贬值，而我们对一段经历的回忆却能年复一年地给我们带来快乐。
Of course, it's not always that simple.
当然，事情并非总是那么简单。
Other studies have suggested that happiness gained from experiences might depend on your personality type, and how many possessions you already have.
其他研究表明，从体验中获得的快乐可能取决于你的性格类型以及你已经拥有多少物质财产。
People with more introverted personality types may get less benefit from social occasions and those with few possessions may get greater benefit from objects.
性格更内向的人可能从社交场合中获益较少，而物质财产较少的人可能从物品中获益更多。
However, for many of us, it could be that when choosing how to spend our disposable income, we'll get far more benefit by spending on something to do, rather than something to have.
然而，对我们许多人来说，在决定如何花掉可支配收入时，把钱花在做事上，而不是花在拥有东西上，可能会带来更多的好处。